<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Insert coin</title>
    <link>https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Insert coin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scala3 typeclassery with graphs</title>
      <link>https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/scala3-typeclassery-graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/scala3-typeclassery-graphs/</guid>
      <description>Before anything I wrote this thing to see for myself if a typelevel style library for graphs makes any sense. It turns out I LIKE IT! but if you&amp;rsquo;re coming from Python, Java, Go or Kotlin you migh will find it odd. In fact even typeclasses themselves are quite controversial, this comment from Don Syme (the creator of F#) caught my eye and it&amp;rsquo;s interesting to see that even in a functional and strongly typed language such as F# typeclasses are (to put it mildly) NOT WELCOMED!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Index Common Crawl with Elasticsearch without a running cluster</title>
      <link>https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/offline-cc-index-spark-elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabianmurariu.github.io/posts/offline-cc-index-spark-elastic/</guid>
      <description>Common Crawl is an amazing project I&amp;rsquo;m always surprised when people I talk to are unfamiliar with Common Crawl, it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most surprising and empowering projects in a world where governments and corporations seem hell bent on taking power away from us.
The projects is host to 8 year of web data grouped in 3 main categories: raw web page, metadata extracts and text extracts with derivative work such as a file index as well as a link graph with ranking for top domains and every page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
